ntfs.com 2016-11-30

# NTFS.com: Privacy Policy and Terms of Use

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which LSoft Technologies Inc., (later referred to as the "Company") collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from the "Users" (as applies to each individual User) of the http://ntfs.com/ website (later referred to as the "Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by the Company.

### Personal identification information

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our Site, place an order, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources which the Company makes available on its Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, credit card information. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personal identification information, except that it may prevent the User from engaging in certain Site related activities.

### Non-personal identification information

The Company, may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

### Web browser cookies

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

### How we use collected information

The Company may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

  * To improve customer service Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.
  * To process payments The Company may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.
  * To run a promotion, contest, survey or other Site feature To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.
  * To send periodic emails

The Company may use the email address to send them information and updates pertaining to their order. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site.

### How we protect your information

The Company adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site. Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures.

### Sharing your personal information

The Company do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. The Company may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

### Changes to this privacy policy

The Company has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site, revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. The Company encourages Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

### Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and terms of service. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

#### Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at: 

LSoft Technologies Inc.  
<http://www.lsoft.net/>  
2550 Argentia Road, Suite 218  
Mississauga, Ontario  
L5N 5R1  
Canada  
+1 (877) 477-3553  
+1 (905) 812-8434  

This document was last updated on January 30, 2014
